# **Gocha Ugulava**

@	gochaugulava@gmail.com	
C	+995 577 77 66 11	□ 2 □ 29 2 0 □ 24 0 1
O	http://gochaugulava.github.io (Personal Portfolio)	
<b>(</b>	www.linkedin.com/in/gochaugulava	

#### skills and areas of interest:

- Economics, Mathematical Methods in Economics
- Data Science, Machine Learning, Deep Learning
- Artificial Intelligence Applications in Economics, Artificial Neural Networks

#### education:

PhD in economics, Kutaisi University Engineer, Kutaisi Technical University

### courses:

- Machine Learning Stanford University
- Machine Learning (with honor) Stepik (OmGTU)
- Programming on Python (with honor) Stepik (Bioinformatics Institute)
- Scientific Computing with Python FreeCodeCamp
- Data Analysis with Python FreeCodeCamp
- Statistics-1-2 (with honor) Stepik (Bioinformatics Institute)
- Data Analysis in R (with honor) Stepik (Bioinformatics Institute)
- Data Science Eduonix
- CS in JavaScript (Golden) BitCamp, CodeHS
- Responsive Web Design FreeCodeCamp
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures FreeCodeCamp
- Front End Libraries FreeCodeCamp
- APIs and Microservices FreeCodeCamp

#### tech stack:

- Python, R, JavaScript , C, Fortran, Basic
- numpy, pandas, scipy, scikit-learn, tensorflow, keras, matplotlib, seaborn
- sql, mongodb
- webdev full stack MERN html, css, js, bootstrap, react, node js, express

#### publications:

- Niko Chikhladze, Gocha Ugulava Regional Economic Development Inequality Research in Georgia by PCA Method. Economic Alternatives 2022, Vol. 28, Issue 1, pp. 35-51.
- Gocha Ugulava Review Of Theoretical Approaches To Using Of Artificial Intelligence For Planning Problems In Economics. Economic profile. 2021, Volume 16, №2 (22)

- Niko Chikhladze, Mirza Khidasheli, Gocha Ugulava Economic Development of Georgia in the Context of Covid-19. Macroeconomic and Regional Aspects. Monograph. Kutaisi University. 2021. 124 pages. ISBN 978-9943-473-64-3
- Gocha Ugulava Use of Artificial Neural Networks to Predict Territorial Economic Indicators. Globalization And Business, #8, 2019, pp. 143-146
- Niko Chikhladze, Gocha Ugulava The Role of Strategic Planning for Local Territorial Development. Innovative Economics and Management N1, 2016 pp. 121-128.
- Tskaltubo Municipality Economic Development Plan. 2007 50 p. Gocha Ugulava Coordinator of The Working Group, Author. Published in the Frames of CHF-Georgia and USAID-Funded Project.
- Tskaltubo District (Information-Analytical Review) Guram Sopromadze, Gocha Ugulava. 36 p. 2005
  Published by the Tskaltubo District Councils Association, Funded by the United States Agency for
  International Development and Urban Institute.

# experience:

2018 - Kutaisi University, Lecturer

2012-2016 - Tskaltubo Municipality Council

2008-2012 - Majoritarian MP Bureau Head

2000-2008 - Tskaltubo Municipality Board

2000 - Tskaltubo District Council

1994-2000 - Kutaisi Arts Lyceum Deputy Principal

## scientific projects:

2021 – "Research on the Regional Economic Development of Georgia in the Conditions of COVID-

19", Kutaisi University, Research Assistant

## summary:

The combination of knowledge in the field of Economics and IT allows me to develop and deepen my skills necessary for effective work. The topic of my dissertation and publications relate to the issues of strategic planning, methodology, performance evaluation, development and forecasting of indicators, computer-mathematical modeling of processes. They focus on modern methodologies using machine learning algorithms, data analysis and artificial neural networks.

Over the years of working in leadership positions in local governments and teaching (including at the university), I have developed the skills of successful teamwork, communication, cooperation, responsibility, planning, organizing and managing workflow, decision making and problem solving.

Certain knowledge and experience in these matters are good prerequisites for success.

June, 2022